Stock Market Live Updates: Indian indices were trading lower on Wednesday dragged by metals, financials, and heavyweight RIL. Meanwhile, the sentiment was also weighed by caution in global peers ahead of the US Federal Reserve’s interest rate decision. Get la…India's batsmen will be in for a stiff challenge but Sunil Gavaskar has backed one of their premier players to have a rollicking series in England. | CricketShraddha Kapoor sings in new video that she shared on Instagram. Check it out here. | BollywoodUnderstanding the molecular biology of SARS-CoV-2 and the COVID-19 pandemic: current situation of available treatments, vaccinations, and emerging strainsIndia has reported 62,224 new Covid cases in the last 24 hours, slightly higher that yesterday's figures. The death count climbed to 3,79,573  with 2,542 fresh fatalities. The dip comes amid warnings of a resurgence in cases with the easing of curbs.The tipping point for irreversible global warming may have already been triggered, the scientist who led the biggest-ever expedition to the Arctic warned on Tuesday.Coronavirus has changed our lives completely. While the times have been really tough, people have become more awareWorried that 390 of its residents got a “spurious vaccine”, an upper-crust housing society in Kandivli (W) has complained to police about being “taken for a ride” by a group of people who held a CoviThe early withdrawal of US and NATO forces from Afghanistan will be a major concern for Islamabad as the cross border attacks in KP and Balochistan are likely to increase as both the Taliban and the Afghan government are going to battle it out for Kabul on Du…As India begins to gradually find its feet after a debilitating second wave of the dreaded Coronavirus, it is just as important to look back as it is to look forward.Analysts have ascribed a 'subscribe' rating to the IPO citing the strong financials of the company amid expectations of a rise in demand for packed & branded milk products post-pandemic.Despite France being odds-on favorites to win the Euros, this isn’t the way Low and Germany wanted to start the tournament.Twitter and several journalists have been named in an FIR (first information report) in Uttar Pradesh's Ghaziabad over "flaring communal sentiments" after an elderly Muslim man alleged that he was assaulted.Veteran actor-director Neena Gupta, who had welcomed daughter Masaba Gupta out of wedlock, revealed in her autobiography 'Sach Kahun Toh' that her close friend Satish Kaushik offered to marry her.Twitter has lost its legal protection in India from prosecution over users' posts because of its failure to comply with new rules requiring it to appoint key officers based in the country, government sources said today.In a series of tweets, the West Bengal home department said the contents of governor Jagdeep Dhankhar's letter to chief minister Mamata Banerjee were "not consistent with real facts". | Latest News IndiaPetrol and diesel rates have been on the rise since 4 May when oil marketing companies ended their 18-day-long halt on rate revision in view of the state assembly electionsNew York--For the first time since 2017, Americans can see a solar eclipse from their backyard.Early in the morning of Thursday, June 10, the moon blocks the sun and casts a shadow on the earth.In CanOnePlus Nord CE 5G will go on open sale in India today, June 16, from 12pm (noon). The phone was launched last week as a new budget friendly offering with 5G connectivity. OnePlus Nord CE 5G is offered in three configurations and three colour options.The flare-up, a first test for Israel's new government, followed a march in East Jerusalem on Tuesday by Jewish
nationalists that had drawn threats of action by Hamas, the ruling militant group in Gaza.From multi-device encryption to sticker suggestions, take a look at some of the most interesting new features and changes coming to WhatsApp in the future.Being an essential nutrient required by the body, carbs have an essential role to play which cannot be replaced by any minerals and vitamins.The three orders by the Delhi High Court are perhaps the first instance of a court calling out alleged misuse of the UAPA against individuals in cases that do not necessarily fall in the category of "terrorism" cases.India News: Now the Lok Janshakti Party (LJP) has officially split into two, with the rival factions claiming to be the "real" edition and enacting the by now famSung by singer Hariharan, the song titled 'Galwan ke Veer' highlights the valour of the Indian soldiers guarding the Galwan and says the "heroes" had risen to the occasion when challenged on the mountains. | Latest News IndiaBoth goals were scored by Afghanistan players as goalkeeper Ovays Azizi dropped a routine catch into his own goal in the 75th minute to give the Indians the lead.With a wealth of talent at their disposal, India must decide if they will deploy both Ashwin and Jadeja or take a seam-heavy attack into the WTC final against New ZealandTwo spacewalks are needed to install the first two of six new solar blankets, giving station power a needed boost.Will Target have a restock this week?Realme has released its Watch 2 and 2 Pro to the European market today (June 16, 2021), during an event also rumored to reveal the OEM's first-gen laptop. This did not transpire as anticipated, although the launch did show the brand is making further inroads …India News: Serum Institute of India (SII) and Bharat Biotech (BB) are seeking higher prices for Covid-19 vaccines from the Centre amid concerns that the cost ofAnupam Kher shared an old picture in which he was seen posing with Shah Rukh Khan and Jackie Shroff. The picture appeared to be taken at a Bollywood party. | BollywoodThe integrated operations team of NASA’s Exploration Ground Systems (EGS) and prime launch processing contractor…Aamir Khan expressed his love and gratitude to the team of Lagaan as well as the seniors of the film industry and the audience for showering the movie with so much appreciation.Taking to Twitter, the official handle of the Russian vaccine affirmed that Sputnik V's efficacy is better on the Delta variant than any other vaccine that published results on the strain so far.31 reported Serious Adverse Events Following Immunisation (AEFI) cases following Covid-19 vaccinationAs many as 50 BJP MLAs led by Suvendu Adhikari handed over a memorandum to West Bengal Governor Jagdeep Dhankhar on four points including anti-defection law and incidents of Tiljala and Chandan Nagar on Monday.