Follow the latest updates on the pandemic in the UK and across the worldSeveral soap stars from EastEnders, Coronation Street, Emmerdale and Hollyoaks have turned their back on acting to take on normal jobs, including working as B&M security guards, barmaids and cheesemakersThe monarch has remained largely silent on matters concerning Meghan Markle and Prince Harry, but she could be set to change all that in a bid to correct inaccuraciesHolidaymakers in the seaside town close to the summit were fascinated by the cavalcade of G7 security. And local traders saw a chance to make some moneyBT AND Virgin might have some of the fastest broadband speeds in the UK but a smaller rival is now offering ultra-quick internet at a much lower price.With famous users leading a rebrand, bedroom accessories lose their stigma in a £90bn health and wellness boomThe Royal Family is seen as a diplomatic asset for the UK and the Queen's meeting with the Bidens will be the second this week.The prime minister’s dishonest diplomacy and willingness to jeopardise Northern Ireland’s stability for Brexit will greatly diminish Britain’s role in the worldPost-lockdown supply bottlenecks are bad enough, but our politicians' fixation on Elon Musk will send prices rocketing in the long-termSky News speaks to Bridesmaids actress Rose Byrne, who stars as a housewife turned aerobics guru in new TV series Physical.With cases of the more transmissible delta variant increasing, the coronavirus restrictions are likely to remain for a bit longer.Migrant labourers tell of being forced to isolate in brutal conditions as Covid wave grips regionThe cover looks absolutely stunningIsrael's long-term leader is set to be unseated by a coalition of parties which united against him.Sir David warns world leaders that humans may be "on the verge of destabilising the entire planet".But faced with online rivals, the company is switching focus from sales to servicing, especially of electric carsWho will Southgate pick?The mystery auction winner will be part of the the first human flight by space company Blue Origin.Britain has pulled out all the stops in a bid to impress G7 world leaders.In a moment, we were reminded how fragile life is. We will all pray that the former Tottenham midfielder makes a full recoveryNews, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the worldʼs leading global business publicationWashington-Moscow relations at lowest point in years, says Russian presidentBritain will have a six-week window to open up in the summer or risk keeping Covid-19 restrictions in place until next year, ministers fearColby Covington says Leon Edwards isn’t deserving of a title shot.Nasa has assembled the key elements of its powerful SLS rocket.Novak Djokovic goes for his 19th Grand Slam title in Sunday's French Open final, where Greek opponent Stefanos Tsitsipas bids for his first.Aer Lingus regional flights operated by Stobart Air between Belfast and Leeds have been cancelled, but will be operating again on SundayA second man has been charged in the shooting last month of Black Lives Matter activist Sasha Johnson, the London Metropolitan Police said in a statement Saturday.The body of Olivia Gimeno, six, was found on Thursday six weeks after she and sibling Anna Gimeno, one, disappeared from Tenerife along with dad Tomas Gimeno, 27‘In order to have an irreversible roadmap, we’ve got to be cautious,’ the PM saidARTHRITIS symptoms can include joint pain, inflammation, and restricted movement. You could lower your risk of arthritis pain by making just a few changes to your daily diet. These are the best spices to protect against joint pain.- How to watch the solar eclipse in the UK and US?- How to watch the solar eclipse safely- What is a solar eclipse?- Solar eclipse conspiracy and doomsdayAmerica’s public health agency has issued a denial that Covid-19 vaccination makes people magnetic in response to a viral conspiracy theory.The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention updated theUntil now, Nasa’s models for the cancer risk of space radiation were built on data from Hiroshima and Nagasaki survivors, ‘not from real experiments in space’The European Medicines Agency’s (EMA) safety committee has added another rare blood condition to the potential side effects of AstraZeneca’s vaccine, as the UK regulator weighs precautionary advice over capillary leak syndrome.Red flags are flying on the red planet after Beijing said its rover had left the “country’s imprint” on Mars as it released a selfie-style picture showing the vehicle and its landing platform bearing